# THOMAS GUERENA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



# **EXPERIENCE**

Spring - Summer, 2015

## University Capstone Project (ffosbr.js)

Technical Lead / Software Engineer Collaborated with Mozilla to create a backup and restore utility library for Firefox OS devices. Integration into OS forthcoming.

Summer 2014 - Summer 2015

#### **iServeLife**

Back-end Architect / Front-end Engineer Web application connecting users to non-profit volunteer opportunities based on personal interests. UI/UX design.

Summer 2013 - Fall 2014

## Kokonect

Full-stack Engineer

Interactive campus map application for Lewis & Clark College.
UI/UX design. Managed client feedback and test groups.

Summer 2012 - Summer 2013

# **Vernier Software**

Software Intern

Built the Labquest 2 updater, still being used by thousands of customers. Performed software maintenance and research.

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm Thomas Guerena

a Software Engineer in Portland, Oregon.

I have 3 years of experience as a javascript engineer. However, I have a boad spectrum of interests and abilities. I enjoy ttttworking with clients, designing applications as much as I do cryptography and AI (almost). Please read more about me on my website, thomasguerena.com.

# **EDUCATION**

2010 - 2015

#### **Computer Science**

Bachelor of Science, Portland State University

#### **Mathematics**

Minor, Portland State University

# SKILLS

# TOOLS

Git	
NPM	
Grunt / Gulp	
Bower	
Yeoman	

## CONTACT

#### 5713 NE 13th Ave, Portland, Oregon, 97211

t: 1 541 921 8717

e: guerena.t@gmail.com

w: www.thomasguerena.com

**g**: github.com/thomasguerena **l**: linkedin.com/in/thomasguerena

# REFERENCES

#### Joe Sauer

Supervisor - Vernier Software T: 1 503 690 9156 E: joesauer@yahoo.com

## Ryan Bernstein

Capstone Project Leader T: 1 503 830 2007 E: rlb@pdx.edu

## **Margaret Adams**

CEO Kokonect LLC
T: 1 503 360 5542
E: margaret@simple.com